found me freely
pretty please be ashamed I have to kill
someone here
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'll catch you and when I do
no job too big no score too small
time to pay off the queen oh this is not
a good plan
[Music]
Eradicator
they should be good
I could have stayed at home
onion cilantro yeah
all right
[Music]
now that's more like it
good night
[Music]
matey that's my business and business is
good
we have this in the bag just don't screw
it up
everyone has a plan till they get
punched in the mouth
[Music]
afraid to get in too close
down
point is mine property of roadhog
all right
that little piggy fell all the way home
you check beneath your bed
more like God of being dead
[Music]
more like ovary
I have your present right here I'm on
fire
welcome to the Apocalypse
only other place I can get some decent
Chinese food
go on ask me what the other one says
[Music]
in three two one
get it over with
I'm Crispy with The Rock
they're out of time
just like Icarus
I'm bored
[Music]
for scrapping you
hahaha
[Music]
you're in my house get out
Someday I'm just gonna leave you
I am Unstoppable
[Music]
we got a fish here
do you ever shut up
I'm on vacation leave me alone
we're losing attack
[Laughter]
well
okay
okay ready to go home hog
thank you
three
two one
if you don't like it stay in your room
arrows huh
is where your hookings
no such thing
violence is usually the answer
make some friends down there
I'm going Hog Wild
no
kill hard power
one down one to go
generator scrapped
be out of trouble Nana
[Music]
I will return
no pain no gain
I should make movies chasing money
I don't fly nobody flies
Like a Rolling Boulder
I hate the core
to God
I'm not losing attack
assassins here somewhere
about time you did something useful My
ultimate is almost ready
oh
the reward Fit For A King
black tweens
say bacon one more time
enemy teleporter destroyed
hmm
I want a car
in time
what's mine is
keep your stuff off the table
[Music]
hmm
I've got an eye on them
yes ma'am
apocalypse ain't over
there's no I in team
try and stay out of trouble for once
what's mine is mine
My ultimate is ready come on
like taking candy from a baby
you want some candy
foreign
specimen
who hurt that killed you
stupid boy
what I can't die
close but on the better hog
that's no fun
hungry where's my sheep
try turn
took him long enough
[Music]
I'm alive
it's all gone to the dogs
that little brother
I've killed someone for less than that
stop messing around
hey this work for me
not feeling right
[Music]
oh sweet home
that's more like it
Olympus
I can smell you there I'm always saving
your skin
I'll see what I can do we need to take
down the objective
sort of see ain't over
a little chicken
I saw you at Calaveras
[Music]
what am I a babysitter
oops
snake hair don't care
get on the attack now
almost done hold on
hook line and sinker
ah better
I'm tired of hearing your voice
[Music]
[Applause]
just need to win one more
out of time
attack
go faster or we lose
not bad for a nice guy
enemy turret destroyed
[Music]
shut up
this myth is mine
stop them and it's done
them anyway
we're gonna win
they're not back yet
and they call me a monster
about time
showstopper
keeping my eye on you
let's stop them for good
the gang's all here
she won't bother us anymore
I'm alive
he died
I've seen faster slugs
[Music]
objectives hanging by a thread
Don't Stop Till Olympus
just keep knocking them off
laughs
when it's yours keep pushing we're all
animals
she's here somewhere
Brooke
you again stay away from me
special delivery
I'm burning rubber
close
[Music]
someone finally shut him up
just like always
got the Imposter ma'am
move those bones
I'll be taking that
Nice kill
someone kill her already
a town SmackDown
they're coming right at us
yeah
Road hard time
the flag is mine
don't try to bubble on me
why are we here
fall into Tartarus
how's Boulder taste
cyclopslam
we're in front
nectar of the Gods
be targeting her
[Music]
I don't think
watch it to you
[Music]
find that Shield generator
My ultimate is charging
they're coming through the doorway
sorry Dad
[Music]
focus on the Assassin
you wanna scrap with me
hope you teasers can fight
what's taking so long
let's not screw it up
all take that Thunderbolt back
let's finish this
enough right in the pine
I don't like talkers
fastest song in the worst
I ain't fine on my own
an apartment
I'm in no rush
stop that payload
All Fall Down
running out of time
Hulk headshot done
field generators here
nobody's killing me
come on I'm waiting
peace and quiet
fear the Cyclops
a little more come on
the enemy teams down
slicers
let's not do that again
believe I'm dead this time
slicer yeah
you live alive
they're ahead stop them
bye
thanks for noticing me
now will you shut up
find the teleporter
how's that I speak
keep piling on the objectives
Last Chance stay close
enemy turret here
Coulda left my gun at home
dining well tonight
over here
don't let them take a flag
get on the objective
everyone group up together
that was mine
oh yeah
oh goody
long range hog
get our flag back
unloading scrap
blocking my son
not feeling so good
eat this
so much for defense
God they got him
eliminate the target
right
all right bro
where's that teleporter
what are you looking at
stop them
who are 14 here
ultimate ready
steal stuff to Rob
no way I'm losing
pesky fly
I'm bitched ass bro got something to say
you owe me
returning the flag
I'm taking your shoes my West is Wilder
stop rolling cowboy
why is the payload stopped
move the payload
blue silence would be nice
got a null Trooper here
didn't have enough
get over here
come closer
we need a Healer
they're taking a point
no
someone grabbed the flag
your sky
Cyclops Style
dropped it my castle now
I ate it here
don't like your voice
you look rich
pretty
don't blow it
think I won't
there's the Assassin
Anchors Away
payload moving out
got some power
objectives moving out
that'll do
they got me
what a comeback
destroy the objective
dropped the flag
enemies behind us
cover the flag
I wanna fly
never count me out
oh
God
where's my backup
leads almost Stars
that could have gone better Punk
[Music]
Carnage here
heavy still kicking
see ya brother
I'm fast too
paying attention
how about some help
oh yeah
oh
Divine favor
Detonator coming in
knock them out
what a dump
founder teleporter
going in
where is everybody
got the flag
easy prey blown apart
[Music]
got my wings
they have a flag
smashed through
just do it get our flag back
yeah
monkeys for dinner
I take what I want
no biggie
I'm pretty hurt
that's disappointing
ball down
defend the objective
back again huh
push off
[Music]
that's all of them
you're almost there
where'd she go
don't you give up
guess I'm back
I need healing
enemy detected
they're getting close
enemy Bastion
it's a cake
oh
my God
pick with the robot
they took him from us
post out of that
bury him deep
my moon now you're pushing now
I'm the champ
stop the payload
stay down
assassin's dead
it's gonna blow
incoming
attack now
they've got the bot come here grounded
brought down
kill that assassin you're outnumbered
I'm taking the point
finisher off
back to the dirt
barricades moving
no running
stop the robot
enforce her here
whatever you say
see you bro
scrubbed out
eat them alive
stop the payload
attack the objective
I wouldn't fall for that where are you
going
come on dude
can't walk
score uploaded got the bot
need Shields
thank you
give me Shields no healers close
I'm watching here grab our flag
taking the objective
cramping out
team
disremembered
I see them
never like science
move the robot
I win
get back
finish them off
payload stopped
bring it in
shiny
my Beast now
let's go again
we got him
stop him quick
someone else take it there she is
Talent sniper
on my way
Amplified
this is it
payload moving
objectives hit
no one to heal me
no way
right in the teeth
she'll be right
enough for now
make a bath
waypoints ahead non-fiction
take him down
charge that
scrap em
Hey look
[Music]
that's another
clear them out
good one
you chicken
stop em
fall back
thank you
try me
Sky Oak
dirt
don't mention it
hello birdie
need healing
feeling tough
up here
keep up with me
yes get our flag
over there
forward
eat Flack
too easy
[Music]
this is beautiful
behind you
they took the lead
get rocked let's pillage
on the right
charging up
they took the bot
an cooked
on the left
finish it off
let's go
sweet ass good
I need a nap
post a robot
they're catching up
Mako get out of there
they pulled ahead
set up here
what's the laws
oh really
feeling quick
beaut
join me
I don't think so
step to it
sorry ma'am
yeah
fortified
that's that
okay
press the attack
I'll hook them
oopsie
you're welcome
gotta stop them
he's ours get ready
watching here
give me armor
they're pushing it
oh
put him down
go over here
breakthrough
get over there
stop him get the gist down you go
over here
Mari
defending
hey
really
need armor
that's mine coming
sniper group up yeah
over there
thanks
easy
get down
last one
no
I dropped it this way
hurry up
[Music]
I'm attacking
oh
on me
you ready
over here
copy me
need help
hi
hey
above us
[Music]
yeah watch out
die
got one dropped
gotcha all right
oh
jump up
looking at it thanks
[Music]
bye get up
go
door
give me
thanks
idiot sorry
mine got it
hello
this way okay
gotcha careful okay
later
yeah hi
sure
thanks
[Music]
foreign
okay